Here, we have a function expression.
لدينا هنا تعبير دالة.
It's an anonymous function assigned to a variable called
وهي دالة مجهولة يتم تعيينها لمتغير يسمى
"returnsAFunction" and the return value of
"returnsAFunction" وقيمة
this function is actually, well, another function.
إرجاع هذه الدالة هي في الواقع، دالة أخرى.
It's a function that just outputs "Hello from inside a function!"
إنها دالة تعطينا فقط "مرحبًا من داخل إحدى الدوال!"
to the console. Let's go ahead and assign
إلى وحدة التحكم. لنتابع ونقم بتعيين
the return value of returnsAFunction to a new variable.
قيمة إرجاع returnsAFunction إلى متغير جديد.
Let's call it "newFunction".
ولنسمي ذلك "newFunction".
So as you can see here,
ولذا فكما ترى هنا،
we're invoking the "returnsAFunction" function
نقوم باستدعاء دالة "returnsAFunction"
and assigning that return value to a variable, "newFunction".
وتعيين قيمة الارجاع هذه لمتغير, "newFunction".
So now if we invoke it,
لذلك فإذا قمنا الآن باستدعائها،
we should see the message "Hello from inside a function!"
سنرى الرسالة "مرحبًا من داخل إحدى الدوال!"
print to the console. And indeed we do.
مطبوعة في وحدة التحكم. وبالفعل قمنا بذلك.
One thing we also could have done was just immediately execute the
شيء واحد كان يمكن أن نفعله ألا وهو مجرد تنفيذ
"returnsAFunction" as well just by adding parenthesis.
"returnsAFunction" فقط عن طريق إضافة الأقواس.
So if we type "returnsAFunction",
لذا فإذا قمنا بطباعة "returnsAFunction"،
call it, and then invoke that return function,
وتسميته، ثم استدعاء دالة الارجاع هذه،
we should see the same message printed out to the console.
فستظهر نفس الرسالة بوحدة التحكم.
Great. Hello to you, too.
رائع. مرحبا بك، أيضاً.